Yoshino!
I'm taking Aika home.
Just don't skip class.
You won't have enough credits to pass if you miss one more.
It'll work out.
Later.
Yeah.
See you around, Aika-chan.
Couldn't you at least give him the time of day?
Mind your own business, Mahiro.
I don't get why you hate him so much.
Like, he might not be a good guy, but he's not that bad.
He's just a con artist pretending to be a nice guy.
The kind of guy who could lie with a straight face.
That's harsh.
The time is out of joint;
O, cursed spite...
That ever I was born to set it right!
Episode 1
The Mage
in the Barrel
Damn it, Samon. This was your plan?
Bravo.
Now I'm stranded on an island
with some cheap sandals and a sundress.
I guess it's better than being stuck here
with nothing but my underwear.
But I can't even use magic in this state...
Master Samon.
Is this really enough to stop the princess?
On this island,
she won't be able to acquire the offerings she needs to use magic.
As such, the princess is no different than an ordinary girl.
So the princess...
Yes, she will perish on that island.
That's Samon for you.
He probably put up a barrier to make the island invisible, too.
I won't be able to seek help from outside.
Guess I'm stranded in the middle of nowhere.
Look here, Samon! You better watch your back!
I'm Kusaribe Hakaze,
the strongest mage ever born into our clan!
I'll put an end to your ambitions—
Guess I should gather some food first...
The Defense Force's held a large-scale drill recently,
Eat all your celery, too!
Promise to do it.
aimed at protecting the most remote islands.
The Ministry of Defense made a statement on the drill,
which included new tanks equipped with a C4I system to facilitate intelligence sharing,
as well as command and control measures...
Messages Received
From: Girlfriend
Subject: Tomorrow
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
"Looking forward to our date tomorrow.
If you stand me up again, I'll never forgive you."
Such combined arms exercises are unprecedented.
Defense Force's Large-Scale Onshore Drill
Let's see what we have—
Rumors Around Town
Carrots Growing in Asphalt
Dog with Human Face Spotted!
Balls That Roll Uphill
Flying Pineapple Spotted
Elderly Man Makes Clouds Disappear
How much weight does a simple promise carry?
Hey, do you think Yoshino's cute?
I guess...
But without Mahiro around, he's just another guy.
He's so fine. Why don't you go for it?
I heard a rumor that he has a girlfriend...
I do.
Huh?
Was he talking to us?
Who does he think he is?
Does he think he's better than us?
Takigawa,
have you heard anything from Fuwa?
It's been a month already.
True.
Well, if he isn't dead, he must be out there somewhere.
How can you say that?
I guess if it's his old friend talking that way, he must be all right.
But he disappeared without even notifying the school.
And it is Fuwa...
He seems like the kind who'd cause enough trouble to make the papers.
You're right.
What?
If he's alive, he'd probably be killing someone right about now.
If promises carry weight...
Yoshino!
All by yourself, eh?
This just isn't my day.
Five, huh?
Feels pretty light.
How much is in there?
He's got quite a bit.
Let's hit the arcade, then.
Again?
I can't do it.
I can't take on five guys at once.
But...
But if Mahiro was here...
Fifteen in a row?
Even a child would know to run away.
Fights aren't about numbers...
Besides, Yoshino was with me.
Even though we were surrounded, it was easy.
So in other words, this is all Yoshino-san's fault.
What? I'm the victim here!
I was dragged into Mahiro's mess, so—
Then you should have fled alone.
I couldn't just abandon Mahiro—
Are you stupid?
Not even Mahiro is stupid enough to sit there and take all those guys on alone.
Acting like a victim makes you look even worse.
Hey, now...
Everyone says it.
If not for Takigawa Yoshino,
the police would've killed or arrested Fuwa Mahiro by now.
And it's your responsibility.
This is all your fault.
Hey, Mahiro...
Acquiring what you want isn't just difficult...
It's also trivial.
Even if you got what you want,
it wouldn't make you happy.
Are you Fuwa Mahiro?
Mahiro again?
Excuse me, I am Evangeline Yamamoto.
My friends call me Fräulein Yamamoto.
Unemployed, twenty-eight years old.
I'm not a shady character.
Everything about you is shady.
And what's your profile?
Takigawa Yoshino, a sophomore.
What's your relationship to Fuwa Mahiro?
He and I go way back.
And that's enough for you to visit his family's plot?
Have you heard from Mahiro recently?
Not a word since he disappeared a month ago.
Really?
Really...
Sorry, but this is important.
A gun suddenly shoved in my face...
This is totally surreal.
But...
Two weeks ago,
a young man in his late teens was seen in a certain area.
One week ago,
an individual thought to be the same boy was seen elsewhere.
Both areas are now under quarantine and entrance is strictly prohibited.
Hold on...
The news never mentioned that—
In the second area,
the boy saved someone's life.
When asked his name, the boy called himself
Fuwa Mahiro.
I don't understand anything you're saying...
He really isn't the type to rescue somebody.
That's a terrible thing to say about a friend.
He's a pretty terrible person.
Even when dealing with a beautiful girl?
Say, around fifteen years old?
No, he might've saved her.
Does she sound like his type?
Mahiro had a little sister.
If he saw someone who looked like her, he wouldn't've been able to leave.
He treasured Aika-chan more than anything.
Treasured?
Past tense?
She now rests under that gravestone.
Yoshino, why did Aika have to die?
It's probably like the police said.
Someone broke in, looking for money—
You know what I mean.
Until that day, Aika lived a normal life.
Why did she have to die this way?
And the killer even got away.
We still don't know that for sure.
It's been ten months and they don't have any leads.
Nothing left behind...
No witnesses...
They don't even know if the killer was acting alone.
We just don't know.
The task force hardly does anything anymore.
There's no chance that the case will move forward.
It's absurd!
It doesn't make sense...
Isn't absurdity part of the human condition?
You don't even give a shit, do you?
Well, I guess Aika never did like you...
So, how would you handle such absurdity?
Find her killer and punish them yourself?
Yeah, that's it...
I'll do whatever it takes for everything to make sense again!
I understand.
You really don't know anything?
What should I do?
A butterfly.
What?
Nothing, a swallowtail butterfly just flew by...
What of it?!
Swallowtails spend winter in cocoons.
It's snowing...
A single butterfly could just be an anomaly—
That's impossible...
Unfortunately for you,
I have more than one gun.
Who the hell is this defiling my sister's grave?
Mahiro...
Mahiro, where did you come from?
Over there.
Over there...
I flew here.
Huh?
Anyway, who the hell is this?
Twenty-eight and unemployed, she's Fräulein Yamamoto-san.
Are you kidding me?
I doubt Yamamoto would want to hear that from some flying kid.
I just followed these guys.
Mahiro!
What was your plan if that had hit me?
So, Fuwa Mahiro, you really did meet with a mage.
A mage?
Do you work for the government?
Unfortunately, I'm just a volunteer.
Do you think bureaucrats and politicians believe in magic?
Answer me!
What is your connection to the black iron syndrome?
At this rate, Japan will—
What's your problem?
Not even at point-blank range?!
I like your spirit...
But for now, rest a while.
Well, let's go.
Was there something you wanted to say?
There's so much I want to say, I have no idea where to start.
Then keep your mouth shut.
Hey...
Wait, Mahiro!
Hey!
This city is done for.
Are you okay?
Leave him.
He's already beginning to metallicize.
What? Metallicize?
It's the syndrome she was talking about.
The black iron syndrome...
Like a statue...
It's a psychic phenomenon that turns all organic life into metal.
It's not a real illness,
but it looks like some kind of horrible, infectious disease.
The same thing already happened in three or so regions.
The government's doing what they can to hide it, but they won't be able to forever.
They'll think up some reason to quarantine this area, too.
Then those barricades she was talking about...
Will we be okay?!
Yeah.
When the syndrome's effects hit their peak, you were with me.
Did she do that to you?
No, it was some seniors...
That isn't important right now!
Those guys again? They never learn.
Tell me, Mahiro...
What's going on?
She mentioned it, too...
It's magic.
The family that's using it has this moronic ambition...
In order to gain greater power,
they're trying to awaken something
that must never be awakened.
Return, return, return, return, return.
The black iron syndrome is simply a harbinger.
Once it awakens, Japan—
no, the entire world'll be turned upside-down.
This doesn't feel right...
Feels like I'm in a strange dream, listening to Mahiro speak...
Only one person is capable of stopping those idiots.
The family heiress and the most powerful mage known to man,
Kusaribe Hakaze.
Yet for some reason,
I believe every word...
The most powerful?
Then are you that mage's apprentice or something?
Apprentice?
Well, I'm helping her out.
Hey, Mahiro...
This is a fair trade.
You have no right to imply that I owe you any favors.
You say that now, Hakaze,
but you're the one in trouble without me...
Oh?
So you're saying you don't need me
to locate your sister's killer anymore?
Hey, where did you get that doll?
Is someone else there?
Yeah, he's—
It's coming again. From the sea this time.
Got it.
Tell me its exact origin.
Mahiro!
One month ago,
I found a glass bottle washed up on the beach.
Inside was the doll and a piece of wood.
A message was written on it.
"If you believe in magic
and would trade your soul to have one wish granted,
hammer a nail into this doll."
Even though this island is concealed,
the ocean is still connected to the rest of the world.
The communication method used by oceanographers and castaways...
A message in a bottle.
Even on a deserted island, I can find a bottle among the driftwood.
Once I cast my message out to sea,
I just had to hope the right person would find it.
Guess I have some good luck, after all.
Samon,
even in my underwear, I'm still pretty tough.
With that, I was able to communicate with the mage on an isolated island.
And then we made a deal.
So that's who that was...
In exchange for my help,
I told her to use her magic to find Aika's killer.
Aika's murder made no sense.
Magic doesn't make sense, either.
Maybe two wrongs do make a right.
I will kill Aika's murderer with my own hands.
I believe it...
But...
By the way,
your parents are working in the next city over, right?
They should be safe, then.
Huh? Y-Yeah...
Is your girlfriend okay?
Yeah...
She isn't here.
All right.
How did you know that I was seeing someone?
Oh, someone mentioned it.
This is crazy...
Look, Yoshino...
That's a part of what we're trying to stop!
Return, return, return, return.
Return, divided fruit!
Greatest of all trees, which raises itself above all others...
Return, return, return, return, return.
Return to your beautiful Tree of Exodus!
Beautiful, beautiful. Fruit, fruit. Beautiful...
What the...
When did the whole world go insane, exactly?
I don't care if this world crumbles to ashes.
However, Yoshino...
I'll save it anyway!
The time...
The time is out of joint.
He's just a con artist pretending to be a nice guy.
The kind of guy who could lie with a straight face.
That's harsh.
And I'm a liar, too.
Messages Received
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
The time is out of joint.
O, cursed spite...
That ever I was born to set it right!
Mahiro,
what does a kiss feel like?
You don't feel happiness or sadness when you're dead.
The promise of tomorrow won't ever come.
Hakaze, you'd better keep your end of the bargain.
Can you trust Takigawa Yoshino enough to give him a talisman?
Let's make a deal.
I will kill Aika's murderer with my own hands!
This is where it all began.
Episode 2
He Said
She Was Quite Beautiful